<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bio</string>
    <string name="ibraheem">Ibraheem</string>
    <string name="save">save</string>
    <string name="muhammad_a_arabic_c_570_8_june_632_ce_b_was_an_arab_religious_social_and_political_leader_and_the_founder_of_islam_c_according_to_islamic_doctrine_he_was_a_prophet_divinely_inspired_to_preach_and_confirm_the_monotheistic_teachings_of_adam_abraham_moses_jesus_and_other_prophets_2_3_4_he_is_believed_to_be_the_seal_of_the_prophets_within_islam_with_the_quran_as_well_as_his_teachings_and_practices_forming_the_basis_of_islamic_religious_belief_muhammad_was_born_in_approximately_570_ce_in_mecca_1_he_was_the_son_of_abdullah_ibn_abd_al_muttalib_and_amina_bint_wahb_his_father_abdullah_the_son_of_quraysh_tribal_leader_abd_al_muttalib_ibn_hashim_died_a_few_months_before_muhammad_s_birth_his_mother_amina_died_when_he_was_six_leaving_muhammad_an_orphan_5_he_was_raised_under_the_care_of_his_grandfather_abd_al_muttalib_and_paternal_uncle_abu_talib_6_in_later_years_he_would_periodically_seclude_himself_in_a_mountain_cave_named_hira_for_several_nights_of_prayer_when_he_was_40_circa_610_ce_muhammad_reported_being_visited_by_gabriel_in_the_cave_1_and_receiving_his_first_revelation_from_god_in_613_7_muhammad_started_preaching_these_revelations_publicly_8_proclaiming_that_quot_god_is_one_quot_that_complete_quot_submission_quot_isl_m_to_god_is_the_right_way_of_life_d_n_9_and_that_he_was_a_prophet_and_messenger_of_god_similar_to_the_other_prophets_in_islam_10_3_11">Muhammad[a] (Arabic: مُحَمَّد; c. 570 – 8 June 632 CE)[b] was an Arab religious, social, and political leader and the founder of Islam.[c] According to Islamic doctrine, he was a prophet divinely inspired to preach and confirm the monotheistic teachings of Adam, Abraham, Moses, Jesus, and other prophets.[2][3][4] He is believed to be the Seal of the Prophets within Islam, with the Quran as well as his teachings and practices forming the basis of Islamic religious belief. Muhammad was born in approximately 570 CE in Mecca.[1] He was the son of Abdullah ibn Abd al-Muttalib and Amina bint Wahb. His father, Abdullah, the son of Quraysh tribal leader Abd al-Muttalib ibn Hashim, died a few months before Muhammad\'s birth. His mother Amina died when he was six, leaving Muhammad an orphan.[5] He was raised under the care of his grandfather, Abd al-Muttalib, and paternal uncle, Abu Talib.[6] In later years, he would periodically seclude himself in a mountain cave named Hira for several nights of prayer. When he was 40, circa 610 CE, Muhammad reported being visited by Gabriel in the cave[1] and receiving his first revelation from God. In 613,[7] Muhammad started preaching these revelations publicly,[8] proclaiming that \"God is One\", that complete \"submission\" (islām) to God is the right way of life (dīn),[9] and that he was a prophet and messenger of God, similar to the other prophets in Islam.[10][3][11]</string>
</resources>